[
  {
    "front": "réunion, rencontrer, voir",
    "back": "会"
  },
  {
    "front": "société",
    "back": "社"
  },
  {
    "front": "fleur",
    "back": "花"
  },
  {
    "front": "magasin, boutique",
    "back": "店"
  },
  {
    "front": "jour de la semaine",
    "back": "曜"
  },
  {
    "front": "oeil, suffixe ordinal",
    "back": "目"
  },
  {
    "front": "bouche",
    "back": "口"
  },
  {
    "front": "main",
    "back": "手"
  },
  {
    "front": "pied, jambe, être suffisant",
    "back": "足"
  },
  {
    "front": "corps",
    "back": "体"
  }
]
